Hello friends, welcome to your own
YouTube channel Class Coaching Center.
Friends, if you are already here and are a Common
Service Center operator, then there is great news for you
friends that CSC is going to
start a service, with the arrival of which the
estimate of CSC will increase, so there will be
maximum demand for it in this market and you will be
able to earn maximum money with the arrival of this service
because we serve as a large and in
my opinion, CSC is the best
service. Yes, I threatened that we know that there are
many people who are doing this to
feed their families, but
you Dinesh Tyagi Sir, you have thought that you have
brought some such service which will generate
your income and you can do this center's app
service and not the reader but
it is the main center like and do
its work well and you have earned good money, then I will
tell you which service will become
rich with the arrival of CSC, let's start the video,
but before that, if you are new at this time,
then you are requested to definitely subscribe to this channel
because updates can come every
moment.  We keep getting news about this, so there is definitely a
plan like this,
first of all we get information about it, let's start
and as soon as we know
which is the best service that is going to come
[Music]
that
Ajay,
hello friends, to learn about this new service, let's
come to Twitter
where Dainik Jagran has tweeted, if they
say so, then I am showing you what the
office has tweeted, Josh has tweeted another minute later,
I will show you, you will see, he
tweeted for this purpose,
so it is orchid to say that LOC means and
CCEA, you can make sesame oil Russian,
this is today's tweet of 25th October
and at 7:35 he tweeted
and told them that you
can make it according to CBSE Rail and you must be knowing
that Harold Pit is very important, if you
want to take the settings from one state to another, then without it
you will not be able to take it, plus
if you want to sell any item and
people are buying second hand, then NSC is
mandatory and to make this recipe, how
much office fee do you need
You have to go round and round, the person who
wants to make it keeps going round the office, so they must
know how much money is there in it, so
how to make NFC of your CSC center, then you
can earn a lot in it or it has been given
CT benefit criminal and
crime and criminal tracking network and
system, decisions exactly matching with the explanation,
apart from students were killed and
misplaced paid by promising registration
number, chassis number in India number system
will yes 322 identified fifteen fun in
nature and being up to minutes means that
distance of quality, see this option is given,
it will be made from the second hotel and the
benefit of this will be that you will send your case to
other states, there are many other judges, if you
just want to be, then such is needed
and if you make this gathering, then they will definitely get commission, so
they will
get money for 80, but nothing has been done about its commission
and this is going to be all 40 in one to two days,
I will tell
you the details about infidelity in the next video,
so  The biggest good news is that
kerosene will be produced from this centre.
Let's meet again in the next video. Till then,
thank you. Jai Hind, Jai Bharat, Jai Bhim.